Samuel George Morton Papers 1819-1850 Mss.B.M843
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Samuel George Morton Microfilm (Film 1413), 1838-1844
  - From Joseph B. Gross, 1841 Dec. 30; 20a
  - From F.M. Robertson, 1841 June 29; 21
  - From S.M.E. Gohun? [UNK], 1841 April 8; 22
  - From George C. Leib, 1841 June 28; 23
  - From Samuel Jones, 1841 July 14; 24
  - From Freidricks S___, Aug. 22; 25
  - From Clos-Bey?, 1841 Oct. 2; 26
  - From John Bachman, 1841 Sept. 27; 27
  - From John Bachman, 1842 Feb. 1; 28
  - From John Bachman, 1842 March 5; 29
  - From F. Tooley, 1841 Sept. 1; 30
  - Wednesday Evening Parties, 1840-41 [Wistar Parties?], 31
  - From Andrew Boardman, 1841 Oct. 30; 32
  - From Alfred Elwyn, n.d.; 33
  - From John Vaughan, 1841 Dec. 23; 34
  - From Francis Markoe, 1841 Dec. 27; 35
  - From W.E. Homer, 1841 Dec. 11; 36
  - Description of small species of mouse found in South Carolina by John Bachman, 37
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1841 Oct. 6; 38
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1841 July 5; 39
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1842 Jan. 18; 40
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1842 Jan. 22; 41
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1842 Feb. 17; 42
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1841 Oct. 21; 43
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1842 March 27; 44
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1842 July 6; 45
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1842 Nov. 29; 46
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1842 Dec. 20; 47
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Jan. 4; 48
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Jan. 10; 49
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Feb. 2; 50
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Feb. 14; 51
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Feb. 20; 52
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 March 5; 53
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 March 4; 54
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 April 20; 55
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 April 24; 56
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 May 24; 57
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Sept. 21; 58
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Sept. 22; 59
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Oct. 1; 60
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Oct. 10; 61
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Oct. 10; 62
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Oct. 13; 63
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Oct. 21; 64
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Oct. 28; 65
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Nov. 16; 67
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Dec. 3; 68
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Dec. 11; 69
  - From George R. Gliddon, 1843 Dec. 21; 70
  - From R. Peale, n.d.; 70a
  - From Francis Markoe, 1842 Jan. 22; 71
  - From J.J. Abut?, [1842 Jan. 22]; 71a
  - From A. Clapp, 1842 Feb. 25; 72
  - From Joshua Bond, March 17; 73
  - From S.S. Haldeman, 1842 March; 74
  - From S.S. Haldeman, 1842 June 4; 74a
  - From Charles Lyell, [1842] Feb. 7; 75
  - From Charles Lyell, [1842] Feb. 21; 76
  - From Thomas Hodgkin, 1842 March 1; 77
  - From S.E.H.?, April 12; 78
  - From Lucy W. Say, 1842 March 14; 79
  - From [Anna] Maclure, 1842 April 19; 80
  - Election to China Medical Missionary Soc. of Philadelphia, 1842 March 24; 81
  - Thomas Cope et. al. Petition to deliver lectures at Mercantile Lib. of Philadelphia, 1842 May 3; 82
  - Invitation. Association of American Geologists, 1842 March 10; 83
  - From R[obert] M[ontgomery] Bird, April 24; 84
  - From R[obert] M[ontgomery] Bird, 1842 May 19; 85
  - From R[obert] M[ontgomery] Bird, 1842 June 26; 86
  - Election to Northern Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1842 March 21; 87
  - From Jeremiah W. Walcott, 1842 March 19; 88
  - Constitution of Northern Academy of Arts and Sciences., 1842 March 28; 89
  - From Augustus A. Gould, 1842 April 16; 90
  - From John Lochir, 1842 June 18; 91
  - From D. Humphreys Stores, 1842 June 17; 92
  - From Spencer Fullerton Baird, 1841 June 16; 93
  - From Spencer Fullerton Baird, 1842 Sept. 16; 94
  - From G[erard] Troost, 1842 Aug. 10; 95
  - From E. Ruggles, 1842 April 8; 96
  - From J.E. Hollwok?, 1842 Aug. 18; 97
  - From John L. Stephens, 1842 Aug. 1; 98
  - From Charles Auttion?, 1842 July 20; 99
  - From William Rush, 1842 Aug. 25; 100
  - From Edmund Ravenel, 1842 Aug. 24; 101
  - From Edmund Ravenel, 1842 Oct. 25; 102
  - From Edmund Ravenel, 1843 Jan. 2; 103
  - Membership in National Institution for Promotion of Science, 1840 Aug. 22; 104
  - From N. Chapman, n.d.; 105
  - From N. Chapman, n.d.; 106
  - Election as Vice-Pres. Pathological Soc. of Philadelphia, 1842 Sept. 28; 107
  - From Benjamin F. French, 1842 Sept. 29; 108
  - From A[lexander] Maclure, 1842 Jan. 15; 109
  - From A[lexander] Maclure, 1842 Jan. 31; 110
  - From A[lexander] Maclure, 1842 March 1; 111
  - From A[lexander] Maclure, 1842 Oct. 10; 112
  - From A[lexander] Maclure, 1843 May 17; 113
  - From A[lexander] Maclure, 1843 July 7; 114
  - From A[lexander] Maclure, 1844 Jan. 25; 115
  - From R.W. Norman, 1842 Oct. 22; 116
  - From Charles Pickering, 1842 June 10; 117
  - From Charles Pickering, 1842 Sept. 25; 118
  - From Charles Pickering, 1842 Oct. 20; 119
  - From Charles Pickering, 1842 Dec. 9; 120
  - From John L. Stephens, 1842 Oct. 18; 121
  - From C[harles] W[istar] Pennock, 1842 Oct. 26; 122
  - From John Locke [Cinannati], 1842 Oct. 17; 123
  - From John Locke [Cinannati], 1843 Jan. 23; 124
  - From John P. Mar?, 1842 Nov. 10; 125
  - From John Patton, 1842 Nov. 11; 126
  - From Linnean Society of London, 1842 Nov. 16; 127
  - From Committee of Students of Penn. Medical College., 1842 Nov. 8; 128
  - From F.M. Robertson, 1842 Dec. 13; 129
  - Broadside. National Institute Medical Dept. - Circular, 1843 Jan. 12; 130
  - From Wm. Biddle, n.d.; 131
  - From William Rush, Jan. 6; 132
  - Circular. Series of lectures on Early Egyptian history, archaeology... by George R. Gliddon., [1842 Dec.]; 133
  - From Thomas Fassitt, 1843 Jan. 14; 134
  - Certificate of Membership. American Oriental Society., 1843 Jan. 5; 135
  - From Charles T. Jackson, 1843 Jan. 3; 136
  - From Stephen Grettet, 1843 Feb. 13; 138
  - From Benjamin Silliman, B.S.,Jr., 1843 Feb. 22; 139
  - From John Russell Bartlett, 1843 Jan. 25; 140
  - From D. Gilluns?, 1843 March 10; 141
  - From Hermin G. Farias, 1843 April 1; 142
  - From John J. Audubon, 1841 Dec. 26; 143
  - From John J. Audubon, 1843 Feb. 8; 144
  - From Charles Galland, 1843 Feb. 28; 145
  - From Charles Galland, Friday morning.; 146
  - From F.M. Bridges, 1843 May 19; 147
  - From Henry Abbott, 1843 Jan. 12; 148
  - Election as member of Egyptian Literary Assoc., 1843 Jan. 3; 149
  - Egyptian Literary Assoc., 1843 April 6; 150
  - Egyptian Literary Assoc. By-laws & membership., n.d.; 151
  - From John W. Briges, 1843 March 3; 152
  - APS. Centenary celebration., 1843 March 31; 153
  - APS. Centenary celebration., 1843 May 20; 154
  - APS. Centenary celebration., n.d.; 155
  - From Hermin G. Farias, 1843 Apri. 29; 156
  - From G.P. Porteth?, 1843 March 4; 157
  - From D. Pantalecni, 1843 May 10; 158
  - From E.S. Baens, 1843 May 6; 159
  - From Eliot K. Hacy _____ kt?, 1843 May 17; 160
  - From John K. Kane, 1843 May 22; 161
  - From M. Burrough, 1843 June 23; 162
  - From John S. Hart, 1843 June 17; 163
  - From John_____?, 1841 Nov. 25; 164
  - From John_____?, 1843 June 1; 165
  - From J.J. Spencer, July 2; 166
  - From J.C. Chusmen, n.d.; 167
  - From W. R. Johnson, 1843 Aug. 3; 168
  - From William Rush, 1843 Aug. 8; 169
  - Note. re. Dr. Morton, 1843 Aug. 5; 170
  - Extracts from proceedings of Nat. Institute for Promotion of Sci., [1842 Oct. 15]; 171
  - From E. Clellan, [1843?]Tues.; 172
  - From E. Clellan, 1843 Sept. 1; 173
  - Certificate of Membership. Societé Royale des Antiquarien du Nord, 1841 May 14; 174
  - 1843 April 14, 175
  - From William B. Hodgson, 1843 Sept. 22; 176
  - From Benjamin F. French, 1843 Sept. 15; 177
  - From Charles Pickering, 1843 Sept. 25; 178
  - From J. Lee, 1843 Nov. 22; 179
  - Asiatic Society of Bengal. Letter of ack., 1843 Apri. 16; 180
  - Assoc. of American Geologists & Naturalists [B. Silliam,Jr.], 1843 Dec. 20; 181
  - Assoc. of American Geologists & Naturalists. List of Officers, 1844 May 10; 182
  - From James D. Dana, 1844 Jan. 24; 183
  - From James D. Dana, 1843 Dec. 19; 184
  - Univ. of Pennsylvania. Report on James Morton., 1843 Dec. 18; 185
  - From John Locke, 1843 Oct. 21; 186
  - Historical Soc. of Pa. Request for lecture series., 1843 Oct. 16; 187
  - From William_____?, n.d.; 188
  - From Asa Gray, 1843 Nov. 15; 189
  - From J._____?, n.d.; 190
  - From William Coopee, 1843 Oct. 23; 192
  - From James D. Dana, 1844 Jan. 8; 193
  - From W.W. Bispham, 1843 Oct. 3; 194
  - From W.W. Bispham, 1844 Feb. 12; 195
  - From Alexander Maclure, 1843 Dec. 21; 196
  - From J.Y. Strain?, 1843 Nov. 22; 197
  - From C. Bispham, 1844 Feb. 2; 198
  - From J.K. Townsend, 1844 Feb. 8; 199
  - From J.K. Townsend, 1844 Feb. 21; 200
  - From S.M.E. Gohun?, 1843 Oct. 13; 201
  - From W.W. Dickeson, 1844 Jan. 4; 202
  - From W.W. Bispham, 1844 Jan. 15; 203
  - From Academie Royale des Sciences, 1843 Oct. 13; 204
  - From Francis Markoe Jr., 1844 Feb. 1; 206
  - From William B. Hodgson, 1843 Sept. 29; 207
  - From William B. Hodgson, 1843 Dec. 10; 208
  - From William B. Hodgson, 1843 Dec. 13; 209
  - From William B. Hodgson, 1844 Feb. 14; 209a
  - From Alexander Humboldt, 1844 Jan. 14; 210
  - From Robley Dungleson, 1844 March 1; 211
  - From Josiah C. Nott, 1844 Feb. 7; 212
  - From Charles Cramer, 1843 May 1; 213
  - From B.A. Coates, 1844 March 11; 214
  - From Marmaduke Burrough Wall, 1844 Jan. 25; 215
  - From C. Bingham, 1844 Feb. 12; 216